<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<project name="getcorelibs" basedir="." default="getcorelibs"><description>		 
         Autogenerated Ant build file that downloads core libs for the project.
       </description><target name="getcorelibs" depends="jakarta-ant-present,&#10;           xml-xerces-present,&#10;           xml-xalan2-present,&#10;           xml-cocoon2-present,&#10;           jtidy-present,&#10;           junit-present,&#10;           IzPress-present,&#10;           commons-logging-present,&#10;           jakarta-ant-target,&#10;           xml-xerces-target,&#10;           xml-xalan2-target,&#10;           xml-cocoon2-target,&#10;           jtidy-target,&#10;           junit-target,&#10;           IzPress-target,&#10;           commons-logging-target,&#10;           dummy-target&#10;        "/>

  
  
   

   
        
      
   
  
     The POI project consists of APIs for manipulating various file formats 
     based upon Microsoft's OLE 2 Compound Document format using pure Java.
  

  
     A common misconception is that POI writes Excel files. POI is the 
     name of the project. POI contains several components, one of which, 
     HSSF, writes Excel files. The following are components of the entire 
     POI project.POIFS is the oldest and most stable part of the project. 
     It is our port of the OLE 2 Compound Document Format to pure Java. 
     It supports both read and write functionality. All of our components 
     ultimately rely on it by definition. HSSF is our port of the 
     Microsoft Excel 97(-2002) file format (BIFF8) to pure Java. 
     It supports read and write capability. HDF is our port of the 
     Microsoft Word 97 file format to pure Java. 
     It supports read and write capability. This component is in the early 
     stages of design. Jump in! 
  

  
    just do it
  
    
  
    Why not?
  
  
  Apache Software Foundation

  This software is released under the Apache Software License 1.1. 
           For detailed legal and licensing issues, please read the LICENSE.* files
           in the /legal directory.
  
  
  
    This software includes software developed by the Krysalis Project 
            (http://www.krysalis.org/).
    
    This software started as an extension of the the Apache Cocoon Build System 
            (http://xml.apache.org/cocoon/) by Stefano Mazzocchi (stefano@apache.org)
            and Carsten Ziegeler (cziegeler@apache.org)
    
    This software includes software developed by Clarkware Consulting, Inc.
        
  




  
  
     
             
    org.apache.poi

    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
        
    
 
              
    
    
    

    

            
    
    
    
    
    
             
    
    
             
            
    
  

<target name="dummy-target"><echo message="core libs fetch finished"/></target></project>